jabongworld.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy

JabongWorld.com views protection of your privacy as a very important community principle. We understand clearly that you and your information is one of our most important assets. Hence, you shall must only submit to us only information which are is required accurate and up to datefor availing any of our services Under no circumstances do we rent, trade or share your personal information that we have collected with any other company for their marketing purposes without your consent. We reserve the right to communicate your personal information to any third party that makes a legally-compliant request for its disclosure. We will only keep your information for as long as we are either required to by law or as is relevant for the purposes for which it was collected. 

You can visit the Site and browse without having to provide personal details. During your visit to the Site you remain anonymous and at no time can we identify you unless you have an account on the Site and log on with your user name and password.

We would love to have your comments/suggestions at **_sales@jabongworld.com_**

**DATA THAT WE COLLECT**

At the time you register to become a Registered User of the Site, you will be asked to complete a registration form which requires you to provide information such as your name, address, phone/fax number, email address and other personal information.

If you submit any information to JabongWorld.com to be published on the Site through the publishing tools, including but not limited to Company Profile, Product Catalog, Trade Leads, TrustPass Profile and any discussion forum, then you are deemed to have given consent to the publication of such information so long as they do not pertain to personal information

If you purchase a product or service from JabongWorld.com, we may collect additional information, including billing information, credit card numbers and expiration dates and tracking information from cheques or money orders. 

We record and retain the records of your Account activities when you use the JabongWorld.com services. If you make purchase transactions online through JabongWorld.com, we may collect information related to such transactions including the types and specifications of the goods, pricing and delivery information, any trade dispute records and so on.

In addition, we gather statistical information about our Site and Users, such as IP addresses, browser software, operating system, software and hardware attributes, pages viewed, number of sessions, unique visitors and so forth.

**HOW WILL WE USE DATA**

JabongWorld.com may use your entire collected information to improve it’s marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve it’s content and product offerings and to customize it’s Site's content, layout and to service your account with us, including but not limited to investigating problems, resolving disputes and enforcing agreements with us.

We do not sell, rent, trade or exchange any personally-identifying information of our Users. We may provide your Collected Information to our affiliates and service providers under contract (such as customer care) to support the operation of the Site and our services. We may use your Collected Information to execute marketing campaigns, promotions or advertising messages on behalf of third partiesYour Collected Information may be transferred, stored, used and processed outside your home jurisdiction. In case of a merger with or transfer of business to another business entity, we will transfer your Collected Information to the entity which acquires the business (Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this Privacy Policy with respect to your Collected Information).

We may use your Registration Information to provide services that you request or to contact you regarding additional services about which JabongWorld.com determines that you might be interested. Specifically, we may use your email address, mailing address, phone number, mobile number or fax number to contact you regarding notices, surveys, product alerts, new service or product offerings and communications relevant to your use of our Site. We may generate reports and analysis based on the Registration Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions.

All of your Publishing Information will be publicly available on the Site and therefore accessible by any internet user. Any Publishing Information that you disclose to JabongWorld.com becomes public information and you relinquish any proprietary rights (including but not limited to the rights of confidentiality and copyrights) in such information. You should exercise caution when deciding to include personal or proprietary information in the Publishing Information that you submit to us.

JabongWorld.com will share your Payment Information with banks or vendors relevant to the transaction in order to enable transactions to be completed. In addition, JabongWorld.com may use Payment Information to determine your credit-worthiness and, in the process of such determination, JabongWorld.com may make such Payment Information available to banks or credit agencies. While JabongWorld.com has in place up-to-date technology and internal procedures to guard your Payment Information against intruders, there is no guarantee that such technology or procedure can eliminate all of the risks of theft, loss or misuse.JabongWorld.com shall not be liable to you or any other person for any damages that might result from unauthorized use, publication, disclosure or any other misuse of Payment Information, including credit card information.

The Site may contain advertising of third parties and links to other sites or frames of other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those third parties or other sites, nor for any third party to whom we transfer your data in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

**OTHER INFORMATION**

**Cookies**

The acceptance of cookies is not a requirement for visiting the Site. However we would like to point out that the some functionality on the Site and ordering is only possible with the activation of cookies. Cookies are tiny text files which identify your computer to our server as a unique user when you visit certain pages on the Site and they are stored by your Internet browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can be used to recognize your Internet Protocol address, saving you time while you are on, or want to enter, the Site. We only use cookies for your convenience in using the Site (for example to remember who you are when you want to amend your shopping cart without having to re-enter your email address) and not for obtaining or using any other information about you (for example targeted advertising). Your browser can be set to not accept cookies, but this would restrict your use of the Site. Please accept our assurance that our use of cookies does not contain any personal or private details and are free from viruses. If you want to find out more information about cookies, go to [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) or to find out about removing them from your browser, go to <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html>.

The Site uses technology from Google Analytics through which data is collected and stored for marketing and optimization purposes and data use profiles are prepared under a pseudonym. Cookies may be used for this. The cookies enable recognition of the Internet browser. The data collected with these technologies is not used, without separate authorization by the person concerned, to personally identify the visitors to this website and is not collated with personal data on the pseudonym holder. The permission for data recording and storage may at any time be cancelled with on-going effect.

**SECURITY**

We have in place appropriate technical and security measures to prevent unauthorised or unlawful access to or accidental loss of or destruction or damage to your information. When we collect data through the Site, we collect your personal details on a secure server. We use firewalls on our servers. When we collect payment card details electronically, we use encryption by using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) coding. Whilst we are unable to guarantee 100% security, this makes it hard for a hacker to decrypt your details. You are strongly recommended not to send full credit or debit card details in unencrypted electronic communications with us. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of your information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you. You are responsible for protecting against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer.

**CREDIT CHECK AND FRAUD PREVENTION**

The Payments that you make through the Site will be processed by our company Jade E Services Private Limited, a company registered in India.

We use standard and authorized payment services and our Credit Check and Fraud Prevention policies are aligned to these companies. All disputes would be handled by Gurgaon courts

**CONSENT**

By submitting data to us or our agent or using the Site, you consent to our use of your data in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy.

Your actual order details may be stored with us and you may access this information by logging into your account on the Site. Here you can view the details of your orders that have been completed, those which are open and those which are shortly to be dispatched and administer your address details, bank details and any newsletter to which you may have subscribed. You undertake to treat the personal access data confidentially and not make it available to unauthorized third parties. We cannot assume any liability for misuse of passwords unless this misuse is our fault.

**COPYRIGHT**

We have copyright over this Privacy Policy. Use by third parties, even by way of extract, for commercial purposes is not allowed. Infringements may be subject to legal action. This Privacy Policy can be changed at any time to include / exclude clauses and JabongWorld.com does not bear responsibility for updating Users on the same.

**CUSTOMER TESTIMONIALS AND REVIEWS**

We may post your testimonials and reviews on our Website which may or may not contain personally identifiable information. We may ask for your consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post your name along with your testimonial. If you would like to request to have your testimonial or review removed from our site you may do so my contacting us at **_sales@jabongworld.com_**
